(Raj:)I don't believe it.
(Howard:)Neither do I.
(Howard:)Doogie Howser's been off the air
for like 20 years.
Actually, I read that it's one of
the most popular programs in India.
(Sheldon:)Might speak to a cultural aspiration to have
one's children enter the medical profession.
LEONARD:
I bet you're right.
- I bet they love Scrubs.
- What's not to love?
(Raj:)Excuse me, hello?
(Raj:)My parents are trying to marry me off
to a stranger. What am I going to do?
- I suggest you go through with it.
- What?
(Sheldon:)Romantic love as the basis for marriage
has only existed since the 19th century.
(Sheldon:)Up until then, arranged marriages were
the norm and it served society quite well.
It's the premise of Fiddler on the Roof.
(Leonard:)I'm not a big fan of musicals,
but I love that show.
(Howard:)Me too. Of course,
it speaks to me culturally.
(Sheldon:)Understandable, but there's a universality
to that story which transcends ethnicity.
(Howard:)Let's not forget
it's got some really catchy tunes.
- Oh, yeah.
- Absolutely.
- I know what I'm gonna do.
- What?
(Raj:)Find new friends.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- So who wants to rent Fiddler?
- No need. We have the special edition.
(Leonard:)Well, maybe we are like
Haroon and Tanvir.